[{"answer_ne_tagged": {"TIME": ["9:00 that morning"]}, "docId": "121130pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", "VBD", "VBG", "PRP", "IN", ",", "NN", ",", "CD", "WDT", "NN", ",", "CC", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "IN", "NN", ",", "EX", "VBP", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 65, "question": "How do you guys find out about this, Walt?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBP", "RP", "IN", "DT", ",", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 66, "answer": "Since we're pretty familiar in the community, several people in the community started texting us about, oh, 9:00 that morning, and, you know, of course, there are no secrets in a small town.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121130pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 73, "question": "It really is a wonderful pre-holiday story, isn't it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "RB", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "NN", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 74, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"DATE": ["today"]}, "docId": "121130pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "PRP", "VBD", "NN", "VBD", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "CC", "PRP$", "NN", "CC", "VBD", "RP", "NN", "NNS", "IN", "PRP", ",", "CC", "RB", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NNS", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "CC", "RB", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VBG", "IN", "VBG", "DT", "NN", ",", "CC", "VBG", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "NNS", "DT", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 80, "question": "Have they given any indication to you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "TO", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 81, "answer": "All they said today was that they were definitely going to take care of their family and their grandchildren and set up college funds for them, and then they had some charities they are really into the adoption and so I know that they were possibly thinking about getting another child, and making sure that the adoption community, you know, gets some of their money.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121130pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "."], "qSentId": 82, "question": "Walt, did you buy tickets yourselves for this Powerball?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "VBD", "PRP", "VB", "NNS", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 83, "answer": "We did.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121130pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "VBG", "RB", "TO", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 94, "question": "What's going to happen to Mark's job now with all this?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "TO", "NNP", "POS", "NN", "RB", "IN", "DT", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 95, "answer": "He's not going back to work.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Mark"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121130pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "CC", "RB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "PRP", "VBD", "TO", "VB", "VBD", "VB", "RP", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "NN", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "POS", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 124, "question": "When you took over from the legendary Joe Paterno with all the shame and scandal that had befallen Penn State -- be honest with me, what was really going through your mind?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "RP", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NNP", "NNP", "IN", "DT", "DT", "NN", "CC", "NN", "IN", "VBD", "VBN", "NNP", "NNP", ":", "VB", "JJS", "IN", "PRP", ",", "WP", "VBD", "RB", "VBG", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 125, "answer": "Well, I knew that it was going to be a difficult challenge and so the first thing I tried to do was put together a great coaching staff and I think that's what we've done here.", "question_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Penn State"], "PERSON": ["Joe Paterno"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121130pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NNS", ",", "NN", "CD", "."], "qSentId": 157, "question": "How have you reassured everybody that there's a whole new world now at Penn State and they don't have to worry about it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VBN", "NN", "IN", "EX", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "JJ", "NN", "RB", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "TO", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 158, "answer": "Well, I believe that we have great communication with our players, number one.", "question_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Penn State"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Coach Paterno"]}, "docId": "121130pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 171, "question": "And what are your thoughts personally towards Joe Paterno and indeed, towards Jerry Sandusky?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "WP", "VBP", "PRP$", "NNS", "RB", "NNS", "NNP", "NNP", "CC", "RB", ",", "NNS", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 172, "answer": "Well, you know, I'll start with Coach Paterno.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Joe Paterno", "Jerry Sandusky"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121130pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "JJR", ",", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 285, "question": "How are you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 286, "answer": "I love you more, by the way, and I'm fine.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121130pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["CD", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 288, "question": "Was it really?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 289, "answer": "Five years.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121130pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBP", "JJ", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "TO", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 291, "question": "We had a blast, didn't we?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", ",", "VBD", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 292, "answer": "You do look great, I have got to say.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121130pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "VBG", "IN", "NN", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 308, "question": "How did you feel when you got this back and thought, here we go again?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBD", "PRP", "VBP", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "CC", "VBD", ",", "RB", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 309, "answer": "I couldn't see myself going through chemo again.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121130pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["JJ", "."], "qSentId": 339, "question": "How did you feel?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBD", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 340, "answer": "Relieved.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121130pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "IN", "PRP", "RB", ":", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "DT", "NNS", ",", "RB", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 352, "question": "Is that what went through your mind, that even if there's one percent chance, you don't want to take it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "IN", "WP", "VBD", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "IN", "RB", "IN", "EX", "VBZ", "CD", "NN", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 353, "answer": "No, because I never -- I never believe those surveys, anyway, because they're always wrong.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121130pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP$", "NN", "CC", "VBD", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "RB", "JJR", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "."], "qSentId": 382, "question": "How have your mom and dad been?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP$", "NN", "CC", "VBD", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 383, "answer": "You know, I think my mom and dad took the news far worse than I did.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121130pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["JJ", "."], "qSentId": 420, "question": "You never stop booing the whole time, did you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "RB", "VB", "VBG", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "VBD", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 421, "answer": "Pathetic.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121130pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 427, "question": "He's not trying to bite the baby, is he?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", ",", "VBZ", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 428, "answer": "She's trying to bite him.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121130pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": [":", "RB", "VBG", "PRP", ",", "PRP", "RB", "VBG", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 437, "question": "What happened?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 438, "answer": "-- clearly missing me, you clearly missing me.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121130pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 441, "question": "What went wrong?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 442, "answer": "I do not know.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Howard Stern"]}, "docId": "121130pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "RB", "RB", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 454, "question": "Did you feel that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 455, "answer": "I thought he handled himself really well, because we know him as the Howard Stern of radio.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Jack"]}, "docId": "121130pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "VBP", "NNP", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 467, "question": "What was the truth?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 468, "answer": "They did offer Jack the job.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121130pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 504, "question": "Do you like any of them?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 505, "answer": "I watch them all.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121130pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["UH", ",", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 507, "question": "Who is the worst judge on television at the moment?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJS", "NN", "IN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 508, "answer": "Oh, dear.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121130pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "PRP", "TO", "VB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 525, "question": "Am I allowed back soon?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 526, "answer": "I would love you to come back.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121130pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 528, "question": "When are you in New York next?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 529, "answer": "Next week.", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["New York"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121130pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "WP", ",", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 536, "question": "Would you like another picture?", "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 537, "answer": "Do you know what, I just had my tea.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Tom Hanks"]}, "docId": "121130pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "RB", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "TO", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "VBN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "``", "NNP", "''", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 564, "question": "Was it that -- was it the concept of being able to create this incredible scene that really attracted you to the movie?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "IN", ":", "VBD", "PRP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "VBG", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "WDT", "RB", "VBD", "PRP", "TO", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 565, "answer": "Well, actually, you know, having this plane crash in the movie was a detriment to my possible decision, because I had done a plane crash in \"Castaway\" with Tom Hanks.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121130pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 574, "question": "You need an actor of his kind of brilliance, don't you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "NN", ",", "VBP", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 575, "answer": "Absolutely.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121130pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["UH", ",", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 583, "question": "Does he deserve an Oscar, do you think?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NNP", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 584, "answer": "Oh, absolutely.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121130pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "IN", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 590, "question": "Do you ever stop and think about that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "VB", "CC", "VB", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 591, "answer": "You know, I don't think about it that often.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121130pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "CD", "CD", ",", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 600, "question": "It was about 30 million?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "IN", "CD", "CD", "."], "aSentId": 601, "answer": "Thirty one million, yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121130pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "IN", "CD", ",", "CD", "CD", "."], "qSentId": 602, "question": "And it's grossed what so far?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", "WP", "RB", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 603, "answer": "Well, about 77, 78 million.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121130pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", ",", "PRP$", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "DT", "PRP$", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 604, "question": "How do you quantify in the modern game of movies a real success?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 605, "answer": "For me, my -- I have done this my entire career.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121130pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ":", "RB", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 609, "question": "What does it take to be really top draw?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "VB", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 610, "answer": "Well, I think -- well, I've worked with a lot of great actors, I mean magnificent actors.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121130pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 622, "question": "Is that your reading of it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 623, "answer": "Absolutely.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}]